All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pilots, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It is not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
After a change of plans, Hordy threatens to crush the entire island under the weight of a massive ship.
I told you before. Didn't you hear me? I'll save Shirahoshi. And this island.
Oh, Luffy.
Because I promised my friend.
Straw Hat.
I'll protect them. Every last one!
Son of Scratches.
Blizzard Slice.
Impact Wolf!
Awesome, right?
Movin!
Robeo Paul!
Rinky!
Hika Hika Hika!
Radical!
And Ricard!
Hill memory!
Purgatory!
Morigiri!
Oh, gum gum?
Oh, Ricard!
Shut up!
Stop! I've had enough of you!
Crush them.
Noah.
Kill them all.
They've forsaken their pride as fishmen.
They deserve to pay the price.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Oh!
Aaaaaaah!
Elko-roooom!
Stop Noah! Desperate Elephant Gatlin!
Those officers were like demons straight out of hell.
But they were a joke to the Straw Hats.
I'm glad they're on our side.
Eyes on the sky! Danger's on the way down!
It's Warazumi!
Those officers weren't!
Could have dropped him in a place with less people, dumbass.
Shut it! Keep complaining and I'll drop the next giant on you!
That was downright amazing, Shanti!
Hey Chopper, you mind shrinking down some?
You're totally upstaging my giant robot here!
Frankie! That beam was so cool!
Are you serious? That robot was utterly useless.
That reminds me! Nami!
What is it?
You should really wear a miniskirt.
Stuff it!
I can't believe we're done!
Well done!
Expect it no less from Luffy's crew!
He did it!
It's for real this time!
I promise!
Luffy beat Horny!
Did I hear that right?
Yeah!
The Straw Heads did it!
They beat the new Fishman Pirates!
They saved us!
Wait!
Move an hour!
The Oa's right above us!
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Fire alive!
It's gonna crush every last one of us!
We gotta get out of here!
Neptune's army might trap us in the plaza if we don't!
We can make it!
Those psycho officers can't stop us now!
It's chaos down there!
How's the evacuation proceeding so far?
Only a handful of citizens have escaped to the sea!
The rest are trying to run but all sense of order has been thrown out the window!
To avoid the window!
Aaaaaah!
No!
No, no!
Aaaaaah!
Are you okay?
Oh no!
Are we too late?
PLEASE DO SOMETHING! STOP THAT THING!
STRAWHEAT!
The rebellion has been vanquished, but it was all for naught!
It's over!
No! It's not!
PLEASE DO SOMETHING!
STRAWHEAT! He's still fighting!
He's not giving up yet!
I can horridly believe what I'm seeing!
He still has strength length!
He's attacking the Noah!
It's breaking apart!
He's gonna smash it?
How can anyone destroy a ship that huge?
Well, they can't! Even if it is Luffy!
They might want to prepare for the worst.
Perhaps. But let's have faith in it.
We'll be all right if he can obliterate it before it crashes. But if he's unable to, then we'll call two of him!
It'll be the end for Fishman Island!
Give it everything you've got, Luffy!
Who's counting on you down here? Come on! You can do that, Luffy!
Move!
I believe in you!
Get it!
What's wrong?
I refuse to run!
Are you insane?
The Noah's right above us!
I know that!
I'm not stupid!
But this reminds me!
it makes me think of another pirate who wouldn't cut off him.
Because I think he Morris.
That's sorry lies!
You could do that!
Let's move and do it!
Yo!
OK, aren't you shabatling?
I need words to run!
把它 hit it on his uh- этap 너.
Okay, don't be amazed at yourlege!
Hold the감이 Dun ot!
Go!
Move!
Captain!
What's wrong?
I refuse to run!
Are you insane?
The Noah's right above us!
I know that.
I'm not stupid.
But this reminds me.
It makes me think of another pirate who fought to protect us.
It happened when I was a kid.
Twenty years ago.
I even recall you being there.
You remember?
There was one other human our kingdom revered.
Hell of a hole we got!
Get back here!
No!
What the hell?
You in the mood to die or something?
No way!
What's he doing here?
And why is he siding with the fishmen?
Neptune helped me out of a jam one time back when we were young.
And we pledged friendship over cups of sake.
Please don't kill me!
I promise!
We'll never kidnap mermaids or fishmen again!
You want to mess with my friend's country?
Then you face the consequences!
You snot-nosed-bombs!
You listen up!
This island is under my protection!
You're talking about Whitebeard?
That guy was a living legend!
You trust the Straw Hats that much?
Don't get me wrong!
I...
I don't even like humans, honestly!
And this is our kingdom, not theirs!
But they...
Our minds were made up as soon as we got to the plaza!
With Jinbei's help, we were gonna save this island!
Leave it to me and my crew!
That's what friends are for, right?
The things that Straw Hats said, and they're risking their lives!
We're rooting for you down here!
We know you can do!
Make it happen, Straw Hats!
We're rooting for you down here!
And we know you can do it!
Keep it up, Straw Hat!
You may be a human, but you've got all of our support!
We ain't running nowhere!
Go Straw Hat! We all believe in you!
Please save our country, Straw Hat!
Save us all!
Tear it apart, Straw Hat!
We don't need that soup anymore!
Straw Hat!
Stay Green Whoopie!
How, Straw Hat!
Who, Starhead?
Starhead!
Stop that door!
Destroy it!
Tell it to bits!
Wreck it all!
I haven't even broke half of this thing!
Wait, listen!
This moon is opening up again!
Stay back!
You wanna help?
Stay back and watch!
All that matters now is me tearing this damn thing apart!
Stop, you dumb shit!
Stop falling!
Strike!
Luffy!
You can do it!
Break it apart!
Super!
Fire!
I'm sorry that this had to happen, Father.
Destroying the Noah, it's the only thing to be done.
Strong!
We're losing the ship of promise.
But what can be done?
My people's lives are more important.
Still, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I cannot keep the promise.
Joy Boy!
A little particle!
A
You may stop.
Who's there?
Enough, Luffy! You can't do this! You have to stop! You're going to kill yourself!
Move with me, Hoshi! I have to save the islands!
It's alright now!
It's not alright! Everyone's gonna die if I don't!
Will you just look? Then Noah's stopped!
The Sea Kings? But why?
You're angry! I don't like it when you yell at me!
Hey! We've got bigger problems to deal with!
I don't know what this means, but I think it's a good thing!
They stopped it! Somehow, the Noah's not falling!
What the hell is happening? Are you seeing this? Did the Sea King seriously stop the Noah?
Oh, Luffy! You're losing so much blood from that wound! We need to get you to a doctor!
Yeah, well... It's okay, really... Just as long... As the ship is stopped... I'm just glad... Everyone... Is safe now...
Help me!
He'll be alright...
I gotta admit... That there is one hell of a human!
Yeah, to say the least... He sure is strong, isn't he?
Even if we had been late... The island would have been saved... At the cost of the Noah being completely destroyed, of course...
Well, it's a good thing we did make it then! I sure am glad that Princess Shirahoshi called out to us like that... Just in time...
But I didn't do anything at all! I was just sad!
Not quite... Your will and the will of the human echoed as one becoming a wish... A prayer to us...
Your desire to save your people was so strong, and we all heard it loud and clear... You're not nearly as helpless as you think...
The power of the Sea Kings... Is yours as well... If you are in need... Then we shall heed your call...
People of the Kingdom... I'm not sure what just happened here... I'm not even sure if I can describe it... But... Whatever it was... It happened...
The Noah... It's been stopped!
And it's damaged... But not destroyed...
Freshman Island... Has been saved!
I knew Straw Hat would save us!
He did it!
It's finally over!
Straw Hat!
What a relief!
Fight!
Horty is vanquished, the knower is stopped, and Fishman Island is saved.
Unfortunately, Luffy was gravely injured in the process.
Just as the Fishmen reached toward the future,
a nagging memory of the past could cost their savior his life.
With no time to spare, a true friend steps forward
to tear down the walls of the island's history.
On the next One Piece To The Future, The Path To The Sun,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Chapter 1
Season 1
Season 2
In the còn 1
Season 3